[{
    "Question": "What function is used to scrap the DOM from the HTML element",
    "Answers":  {
      "A": "InnerText",
      "B": "innerHTML",
      "C": "textContent"
    },
    "selector": "q1",
    "CorrectAnswer": "C"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of the following is a list of HTML attributes",
    "Answers":  {
      "A": "src, style, class, href, id, and selected",
      "B": "innerHTML, textContent and innerText",
      "C": "div, span, ul, li, and header"
    },
    "selector": "q1",
    "CorrectAnswer":  "A"
},
{
  "Question": "Where is the coupon stored in the browser before applying  to the site",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "Cookie",
    "B": "sessionStorage",
    "C": "localStorage"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "C"
},
{
  "Question": "Where is the coupon stored under YCP",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "vc.yieldify.com",
    "B": "td.yieldify.com",
    "C": "app.yieldify.com"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "B"
},
{
  "Question": "Which function can be used to decode the stored string",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "byob()",
    "B": "atob()",
    "C": "btob()"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "B"
}
,
{
  "Question": "What is the minimum number of coupons need in coupon carrier for YCP to trigger a campaign",
  "Answers": {
    "A":"1",
    "B": "5",
    "C": "16"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "C"
},
{
  "Question": "Which string will this regex pattern match.    /.{14}/",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "my str",
    "B": "my long string",
    "C": "my string"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "B"
},
{
  "Question": "Which pattern will this pattern fully match.    /\\d{0,4}-\\d{0,2}-\\d{0,2}/",
  "Answers": {  
    "A": "https://www.fellows.co.uk/Watches-Watch-Parts/2018-03-26",
    "B": "https://www.fellows.co.uk/The-Watch-Sale/04-24-2018#low_estimate",
    "C": "https://www.fellows.co.uk/The-Watch-Sale/24-04-18#low_estimate=&high_estimate"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "A"
},
{
  "Question": "The regex pattern will match which string.   /aab+c*/",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "aabc",
    "B": "aab",
    "C": "both of the above"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "C"
},
{
  "Question": "The regex pattern will match which string.    /aab+c+/",
  "Answers": {
    "A": "aabc",
    "B": "aab",
    "C": "aacb"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "A"
},
{
  "Question": "What happens to the text after retrieved using textContent",
  "Answers": {
      "A": "removes all white space and new lines",
      "B": "replaces white space and new lines with a space",
      "C": "replaces extra white space and new lines with a space"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "C"
},
{
  "Question": "What is the character limit YCP will scrap",
  "Answers": {
      "A": "100",
      "B": "256",
      "C": "50"
  },
  "selector": "q1",
  "CorrectAnswer": "B"
}



]
